Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- This is Your Life, 1952-1987; Series 1.
  - Research Material, Scripts and Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Donald Smith, 1977 August 5; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - T. J. Smith, 1976 February 5; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Dr. Edmond Souchon, 1961 February 22; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is a New Orleans doctor and jazz musician. Guests include: Ray Bauduc, musician (drums); Eddie Condon, musician (banjo and guitar); Bob Havens, musician (trombone); Ray Leatherwood, musician (bass); Matty Matlock, musician (clarinet); Mugsy Spanier, musician (cornet).
    - Alfred Southon, 1959 March 30; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Barry Spanjaard, 1983 December 15; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is an American who survived Bergen-Belsen concentration camp.
    - Dr. Frank Sparks, 1953 January 7; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is an industrialist and College President.
    - Tris Speaker, 1949 March 22; script; research notes (Box 57)
      Subject is a baseball player. Guests include: Lena Blackburn, former baseball player (White Sox shortstop, 1914), now assistant coach for the Athletics; Lou Boudreau, Cleveland Indians manager (his boss), "Manager of the Year" 1948; Harry Hooper, former baseball player (Boston right fielder, 1914); Bob Hope, legendary entertainer, friend; part owner of Cleveland Indians; J. T. "Chief" Meyers, former baseball player (Giants catcher, 1912 World Series against Boston); Joe Sewell, former baseball player (Cleveland Indians shortstop); Bill "Wamby" Wambsganss, former baseball player (Cleveland Indians, made only unassisted triple play in World Series history, 1920); Lefty Wiesmann, trainer for the Cleveland Indians since 1922.
    - Johnny Speight, 1970 April 30; script; research notes (Box 225)
    - Victor James De Spiganovics, 1960 November 21; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Maria Spirtos, 1960 September 25; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is a Greek immigrant, Ohio's Mother of America 1958 - who has had a lifetime of hardships.
    - Maria Spirtos, 1960 September 25 (Box 233)
    - Robert Stack, 1960 November 22; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is a film and television star. Guests include: William J. Davis, was on All American First Team (shooting) with subject; Betty (Mrs. Eliot) Ness, widow of FBI agent Eliot Ness, whom subject played on television; Joe Pasternak, film producer; William "Bill" Shiffrin, agent; William Wellman, film director.
    - Robert Stack, 1960 November 22 (Box 233)
    - Ilse Stanley, 1955 November 2; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is a German Jew who helped 400 people escape from the Nazi regime. Guests include: Fritz Lang, film director, directed her in the film "Metropolis" 30 years earlier when she was a student at the Max Rhinehardt School of the Theatre in Berlin - plug his new movie "While the City Sleeps"; Milton Stanley, husband, actor.
    - Len Stanmore, 1959 December 21; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Joan Stanton, 1963 October 8; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Colonel John P. Stapp, 1955 October 26; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is an Air Force doctor and rocket sled test driver.
    - Mabel Stark, 1950 April 26; script; research notes (Box 57)
      Subject is a circus animal trainer. Guests include: Jorgen M. Christiansen, great circus horse trainer, taught her to do parachute jump on horse; Dolly Jacobs, circus performer, was aerialist with Al G. Barnes Circus who fell 35 feet in 1934; now has elephant act with the Gil Gray Shrine Circus; Mrs. Charles Post, played baritone horn in Al G. Barnes Circus band; Bob Thornton, famous pioneer animal trainer; Eddie Trees, husband, was her head cage man in 1920.
    - Statue of Liberty, 1985 April 15 (Box 235)
      Includes treatement and budget.
    - Commander Gordon Steele, 1958 January 20; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Tommy Steele, 1958 October 27; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Harry Steffel, 1949 January 25; streaming audio (Box 57)
      script, audio. Subject is a man on the street.
    - Casey Stengel, 1952 October 29; script; research notes (Box 218)
      Subject is manager of the New York Yankees. Includes appearances by: Jim Brideweser; Chuck Dressen; Mel Duezabou; Braven Dyer; C.L. "Brick" Laws; Billy Martin; Irish Muesel; Irv Noren; John E. "Beans" Reardon; Charlie Silvera; Duke Snyder; Del Webb; Zach Wheat.
    - Alice Stern, 1963 September 30; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Bill Stern, 1959 November 25; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a sportscaster who overcame his narcotics addiction. Includes appearances by: Joe Louis, former heavyweight boxing champion; Phillip "Phil" Carlin, television producer; Tom Gallery, Director of Sports for NBC; Ray Scott, sportscaster.
    - Jessie Steward, 1958 April 23; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a double amputee/model.
    - Admiral Jim Stockdale, 1983 October 16; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a former prisoner of war.
    - Pansy Stockton, 1953 December 30; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a sun painting artist. Guests include: Charles "Eagle Plume" Burkhardt, Native American, was one of the ceremonial dancers when she was formally adopted by the Ogallala Sioux in 1936 (she had interceded with the government on behalf of the South Dakota Sioux to help preserve their land and rights).
    - Frederick Stone, 1958 March 3; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Gale Storm, 1955 April 20; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a film and television star. Guests include: Lee Bonnell, husband, former actor; Charles Farrell, actor; Rev. Dr. Cleveland Kleihauer, pastor of the Hollywood-Beverly Christian Church; Charles Pomerantz, agent.
    - Major Alan Stretton, 1977 February 1; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Douglas Stringfellow, 1954 January 20; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a Utah Congressman.
    - Ruth Strome, 1956 January 18; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a Yuba City flood victim.
    - Sally Struthers, 1983 October 11; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a television star. Guests include: Rita Moreno, actress; Jean Stapleton, actress; Judy Thomas, television producer; Sheila Renee Bluebird, Cherokee child (age 12) from Park Hill Project in Oklahoma; Danial Brown, actor; Damon Butler, actor; Tina Caspery, actor; Amy Lynn Cresliak, actress; Devonne Dellos, actress; Aaron Hamilton, actor; Christian Jacobs, actor; Angela Lee Sloan, actress; Robert Soap, Cherokee child (age 9) from Park Hill Project in Oklahoma; Justin Sugar, Cherokee and Creek child (age 10) from Park Hill Project in Oklahoma; Jennifer Ursitti, actress.
    - Jesse Stuart, 1958 February 12; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is an author, heart attack victim, and American Heart Association Spokesman.
    - Gloria Swanson, 1957 January 23; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a film star. Includes appearances by: Monte Blue; Edmund Burnes; Francis X. Bushman; Ricardo Cortez; Allan Dwan; Julia Faye; Raymond Hatton; Rod LaRocque; Jesse L. Lasky; Walter O'Keefe; Mack Sennett; Lois Wilson.
    - Gloria Swanson, 1957 January 23 (Box 233)
    - Marguerita Sylva, 1956 March 17; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is an opera star. Guests include: Madame Mariska Aldrich, former star of the Metropolitan Opera; Anna Fitziu, former soprano of the Metropolitan Opera; Robert Hurd, radio program executive in Los Angeles; Edward Johnson, former operatic tenor (sang the role of Don Jose opposite her Carmen at the opening of the Hollywood Bowl in 1922) and former General Manager of the Metropolitan Opera; Leslie Sylva, daughter, sportswear designer; Mrs. Francis Wilson, understudy; Cobina Wright, Hearst columnist.
    - Maggie Tabberer, 1976 September 17; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Kiyoshi Tanimoto, 1955 May 11; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a Methodist Minister and a Hiroshima survivor.
    - Reverend Kiyoshi Tanimoto, 1955 May 11 (Box 233)
      Annotated script. Television broadcast.
    - Rod Taylor, 1975 October 10; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Ron Taylor, 1975 November 14; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Ron Taylor, 1975 November 14; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Leonard Teale, 1976 September 27; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Dr. James Templeton, 1952 November 5; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a doctor.
    - Ellaline Terriss, 1962 May 7; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Phil Thatcher, 1956 December 5; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is an ex-convict.
    - Charles Ward Thomas, 1950 March 29; streaming audio (Box 57)
      script, audio. Subject is a Coast Guard hero.
    - Danny Thomas, 1954 January 27; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a radio and television comedian. Guests include: Michael Curitz, movie director ("Casablanca", "White Christmas"; directed subject in "I'll See You In My Dreams" and "The Jazz Singer"); Earl Ebi, director of the Lux Radio Theatre; Lou Edelman, former Warner Brothers producer, now producer of subject's TV show "Make Room for Daddy"; Margaret Julia Thomas, daughter, later known as actress and TV star, Marlo Thomas.
    - Danny Thomas, 1954 January 27 (Box 233)
      Subject is a radio and television comedian. Includes appearances by: Michael Curitz; Earl Ebi; Lou Edelman; Marlo Thomas.
    - Lowell Thomas, 1959 September 30; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a Author/Traveler/Radio Personality. Includes appearances by: Jack Dempsey; Althea Gibson; Ingemar Johannson; Bobby Riggs, Beulah Bondi, Rev. Bob Richards.
    - Lowell Thomas, 1959 September 30 (Box 233)
      Subject is a Author/Traveler/Radio Personality. Includes appearances by: Jack Dempsey; Althea Gibson; Ingemar Johannson; Bobby Riggs.
    - Edyth Thomson, 1950 May 30; streaming audio (Box 57)
      script, audio. Subject is a school teacher.
    - Dame Sybil Thorndyke, 1960 October 10; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Bertie Wallace Tibble, 1963 February 25; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Casey Tibbs, 1958 May 7; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a rodeo champion. Guests include: Bud Annis, Native American (Sioux), from the Cheyenne River Indian Reservation in South Dakota; Bill Linderman, former All-Around Cowboy rodeo champion; Ken Roberts, former champion bull rider; Jim Shoulders, current All-Around Cowboy champion, top rodeo contestant of the day.
    - Casey Tibbs, 1958 May 7 (Box 233)
      Subject is a rodeo champion.
      Television broadcast. Annotated script.
    - Richard Todd, 1960 March 7; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - General Holger N. Toftoy, 1959 May 13; script; research notes (Box 219)
      The subject pioneered the US Missile Program.
    - Countess Alexandra Tolstoy (Box 295, Folder 3)
      Research notes. The subject is an anti-communist and daughter of Leo Tolstoy.
    - Alexandra Tolstoy, 1956 October 10; script; research notes (Box 219)
      The subject is an anti-communist and daughter of Leo Tolstoy.
    - Air Vice Marshall William Townsend, 1976 April 22; script; research notes (Box 221)
    - Colleen Townsend, 1958 November 12; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject gave up a film career for Church work. Guests include: Patrick Cunning, Television producer, now executive producer of "Lollipop Lane" on KMJ-TV in Fresno, CA; Rev. Louis Evans, Jr., husband, minister, pastor of Bel Air Presbyterian Church; Dr. Louis Evans, Sr., long-time pastor of the Hollywood Presbyterian Church; Mel Shauer, agent; Alan Young, comedian, and character actor, television star.
    - Louise Tracy, 1972 September 26; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject (Mrs. Spencer Tracy) operated a clinic for the deaf. Includes appearances by: Walter Pidgeon.
    - Louise Tracy, 1972 September 26; script (Box 233)
    - Vincent Tracy, 1957 October 2; script; research notes (Box 219)
      Subject is a recovering alcoholic who founded a rehabilitation center.
    - Jack Train, 1957 November 11; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Lawrence Tranter, 1946 April 27; script; research notes (Box 57)
      Subject is a paraplegic veteran.
      First episode of "This is Your Life" which was done as an act on "Truth or Consequences."
    - Tommy Trinder, 1959 May 11; script (Box 223)
    - Harry S. Truman, 1955 November 30; script (Box 235)
    - Harry S. Truman, 1955 November 30; 2 folders (Box 235)
      Includes script and reasearch file.
    - H. Park Tucker, 1956 March 21; script (Box 219)
      Subject is the Chaplain - Atlanta Penitentiary.
    - Eva Turner, 1959 September 14; script; research notes (Box 223)
    - Elizabeth Twistington-Higgins, 1961 November 6; script (Box 223)
    - Tommy Tycho, 1976 October 22; script (Box 221)
    - Agnes Underwood, 1956 November 7; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a lady newspaper editor. Guests include: Thomas Caton, Assistant City Editor of the Herald Express; Perry Fowler, Chief Photographer of the Herald Express; David Hearst, Publisher of the Los Angeles Herald Express; Ed Krauch, Picture Editor of the Herald Express; Bill Pigue, Assistant City Editor of the Herald Express; Edwin L. Stolp, former L.A. motorcycle policeman at Carthay Circle Theater movie premier in 1930's; Gertrude Price (Mrs. W. B.) Wilmott, Woman's Page Editor for the Los Angeles Record newspaper.
    - Agnes Underwood, 1956 November 7 (Box 233)
      Subject is a lady editor.
    - Leo Urbanski, 1950 March 22; streaming audio (Box 57)
      script, audio. Subject is a fire chief.
    - Madame Vacani, 1961 January 23; script (Box 223)
    - Dick Van Dyke, 1987 March 26-April 19; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a comedian and film and television star. Includes appearances by: Morey Amsterdam; Sheldon Leonard; Rose Marie; Carl Reiner; Chita Rivera; Jerry Van Dyke.
    - Mrs. Robert L. Vann, 1953 October 14 (Box 233)
      Jessie Ellen Mathews Vann. Subject is the owner and the publisher of the Pittsburgh Courier. Script is annotated.
    - Mrs. Robert L. Vann, 1953 October 14; script (Box 228)
      Jessie Ellen Mathews Vann. Subject is the owner and the publisher of the Pittsburgh Courier.
    - The Reverend Edward Chad Varah, 1961 February 20; script (Box 223)
    - Calla Varner, 1959 October 4; script; research notes (Box 228)
    - Reg Varney, 1970 May 20; script (Box 225)
    - Frankie Vaughn, 1970 April 14; script (Box 225)
    - Frankie Vaughn, 1960 October 16; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a singer. Includes appearances by: Hetty King, music hall star; Billy Marsh, agent; Joe McGrath, actor, singer.
    - T. Alexander Vaughey, 1969 September 19; script (Box 235)
    - Ralph Veady, 1955 November 30; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a double amputee and success story. Guests include: Joseph Bosio, Deputy City Attorney for the L.A. Department of Water and Power; Bert Clark, former operator of the Polar Palace ice skating rink in L.A.; Cleve Hermann, sportscaster, KRCA head of sports on the West Coast - assists surprise; Richard Nixon, U.S. Vice President.
    - Sara Veffer, 1960 March 19; script (Box 228)
      Dutch Family - hid from Nazis 1,000 days in one room.
    - John Vidler, 1958 November 10; script (Box 223)
    - Count Felix von Luckner, 1959 November 4; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a World War I German Naval officer & adventurer. Guests include: Lowell Thomas, author, lecturer, war correspondent, radio and TV personality.
    - Count Von Luckner, 1959 November 4 (Box 234)
      Subject is a World War I German Naval officer & adventurer.
      Photo script.
    - Joseph A. Walker, 1961 May 29; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a test pilot.
    - Mickey Walker, 1955 March 23; script (Box 228)
      Subject is an artist and ex prizefighter. Guests include: John Anthes, manager; Jack Britton, welterweight champion; Douglas Morrow, Academy Award winning screenwriter, author of screenplay based on subject's life; Maxwell Simpson, noted American artist.
    - Nancy Bird Walton, 1976 November 12; script (Box 221)
    - Mrs. Arries Ann Ward, 1957 February 27; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a 95 year old former slave.
    - Sister Mary Ward, 1958 September 7; script (Box 223)
    - Lucille Warnecke, 1959 March 31; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a polio victim who adopted Japanese children.
    - Harry Warren, 1958 March 19; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a song writer. Includes appearances by: Alice Faye; Mack Gordon; Ruby Keeler; Guy Lombardo; Johnny Mercer; Walter Scharf.
    - Coy and Goldie Watson, 1958 September 18; script (Box 228)
      Subjects were silent film pioneers who had nine children. Includes appearances by family members who were child actors: Bill Watson; Bobs Watson; Delmar Watson; Garry Watson; Harry Watson.
    - Madge Watson and Elsie Wood, M.B.E., 1964 January 6; script (Box 225)
    - Dennis Weaver, 1957 December 11; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a television star. Includes appearances by: Lonny Chapman, actor, writer, director in New York City; Charlton Heston, actor.
    - Henry Webb, 1960 February 15; script (Box 223)
    - John Weber Jr., 1955 October 19; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a former mental patient.
    - Francis Weeks, 1950 May 3; streaming audio (Box 57)
      script, audio. Subject is a truck driver.
    - Harry Welchman, 1960 February 8; script (Box 223)
    - Lawrence Welk, 1957 March 6; script (Box 228)
      Subject is an orchestra leader and TV star. Guests include: Chuck Coffee, musician; Lennon Sisters.
    - Lawrence Welk, 1957 March 6 (Box 233)
      Subject is an orchestra leader/TV star. Includes appearances by: The Lennon Sisters.
    - William Wellman, 1954 December 8; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a film director. Includes appearances by: James Cagney; Robert Fellows; Hedda Hopper; Tab Hunter; Diana Lynn; Fred MacMurray; David O. Selznick; Jan Sterling; John Wayne; Teresa Wright.
    - William Wellman, 1954 December 8; script (Box 233)
      Subject is a film director.Includes appearances by: James Cagney; Robert Fellows; Hedda Hopper; Tab Hunter; Diana Lynn; Fred MacMurray; David O. Selznick; Jan Sterling; John Wayne; Teresa Wright.
      Annotated.
    - Michael Wendon, 1977 June 2; script (Box 221)
    - Emma Jo Wengert, 1954 May 12; script (Box 228)
      Subject was falsely imprisoned for murder.
    - Jackson Wheeler, Jr., 1961 June 9; script (Box 228)
      Subject is a young adventurer. Guests include: Chief Tangamashi, Jivaro medicine man; Nicta, Jivaro medicine man; Bill Leyden, television host.
    - Mr. Albert Whelan, 1957 September 30; script (Box 223)
    - Betty White, 1987 March 23; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a television star. Guests include: Bea Arthur, actress; Ed Asner, actor; Frank DeVol, musical director on her early TV variety show; Georgia Engel, actress; Estelle Getty, actress; Mark Goodson, producer of TV game shows ("Password," "Match Game," etc.); Johnny Grant, "Mayor of Hollywood", radio and TV personality; Valerie Harper, actress; Cloris Leachman, actress; Gavin MacLeod, actor; Rue McClanahan, actress; Mary Tyler Moore, actress; Jack Paar, television talk show host; Gene Rayburn, host of "Match Game"; Grant Tinker, former head of MTM Productions, former NBC Chairman of the Board; Robert Whitten, drama teacher at Beverly Hills High School.
    - Betty White, 1987 April 19; script (Box 57)
    - Lee Roy "Lasses" White, 1949 March 1; streaming audio (Box 233)
      Two copies of annotated scripts. Audio. Subject is a Vaudeville/film star. Guests include: Jimmie Cooper, minstrel showman and singer; Peeny Elmo, minstrel showman; Jimmy MacDonald, minstrel showman; Skeets Mayo, minstrel showman; Verne Phelps, minstrel showman; Ernest Reeves, minstrel showman, singer; William T. Speath, manager; John Swar, minstrel showman, half of team Swar & Mack, the original Two Black Crows; Chester Wilson, minstrel showman.
      For radio broadcast.
    - Lee Roy "Lasses" White, 1949 March 1; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a Vaudeville/film star.
    - Robb White, 1959 January 28; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a writer who bought and lived on a tropical island. Guests include: William Castle, producer-director; Von Dexter, TIYL Musical Director; Dr. John White, brother, scientist with the Smithsonian Astro-Physical Observatory.
    - Thelma White, 1957 May 29; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a Vaudeville Star/Agent who survived a serious illness. Guests include: Armida, Latin-American star of stage and screen; Robert Blake, one of a group of six struggling young actors she represents; became star of TV's "Baretta"; Gaylord Carter, radio, television and recording artist (organist); Rosetta Duncan, vaudeville star, one of the Duncan Sisters; Vivian Duncan, vaudeville star, one of the Duncan Sisters.
    - Vic Willcox, 1963 March 18; script (Box 223)
    - Bransby Williams, 1958 December 8; script (Box 223)
    - Mae Williams, 1955 February 9 (Box 233)
      Subject is a Singer who overcame great adversity.
      Television broadcast annotated script. Guests include: Lou Costello, comedian, (part of team Abbott and Costello) - bought The Band Box (small Hollywood nightclub where she was performing) in 1943 and became her personal manager; Arthur Kachell, drama teacher at Hollywood High School; Beatrice Kay, singer; Janis Paige, movie and Broadway musical star; Danny Thomas, comedian, TV star.
    - Marjorie Williams, 1954 April 21; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a Past Director, Hollywood Studio Club.
    - Roger Williams, 1959 April 8; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a pianist/composer. Guests include: Bob Barker, host of "Truth or Consequences"; Milton Berle, TV star; Joe Conn, TIYL Tech Director; Dick Gottlieb, TIYL director; Stan Greeson, manager; Hal Kanter, Berle's director; David Kapp, Head of Kapp Records; Teddy Wilson, jazz pianist; subject's teacher at Julliard School of Music in New York City, 1951.
    - Ted Willis, 1959 March 23; script (Box 223)
    - Earl Wilson, 1971 September 14; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a columnist. Guests include: Marty Allen, comedian; part of team Allen & Rossi; Cliff Arquette, comedian and actor; Wally Cox, bespectacled comedian and actor who usually played meek characters; Arte Johnson, actor and comedian, regular on TV's "Laugh-In"; Michelle Lee, actress; Paul Lynde, comedian, TV, Broadway and movie actor; Rose Marie, comedienne; Peter Marshall, host of "Hollywood Squares"; Earl Lyons Wilson, son, singer, composer.
    - Earl Wilson, 1971 September 14 (Box 233)
      Subject is a columnist.
    - Helen Wilson, 1961 April 4; script (Box 223)
    - Marie Wilson, 1958 December 31; script (Box 57)
      Subject is a comedienne/humanitarian. Guests include: Ida Mayer Cummings, founder and for 20 years President of the Junior Auxiliary of the Jewish Home for the Aged in Los Angeles (sister of Louis B. Mayer); Robert "Bob" Dachman, Midwest Director of the City of Hope; Robert "Bob" Fallon, husband, movie and television producer; Bryan Foy, film producer; Cy Howard, film, television and radio producer, director and writer - created, produced and directed "My Friend Irma" on radio; Joe Kievit, Los Angeles Director of the March of Dimes; Jack Latham, NBC newscaster; Cathy Lewis, radio, television and movie actress, co-star on "My Friend Irma"; Ken Murray, producer-star of musical revue "Blackouts"; Mary Sale, television producer.
    - Michael Wilson, 1962 December 10 (Box 223)
    - Godfrey Winn, 1961 April 12; script (Box 223)
    - Teddy Winn, 1964 February 17; script (Box 223)